Create and manage identities including keys and addresses

Usage: stellar.exe keys [OPTIONS] <COMMAND>

Commands:
  add         Add a new identity (keypair, ledger, OS specific secure store)
  public-key  Given an identity return its address (public key) [aliases: address]
  fund        Fund an identity on a test network
  generate    Generate a new identity using a 24-word seed phrase The seed phrase can be stored in a config file (default) or in an OS-specific secure store
  ls          List identities
  rm          Remove an identity
  secret      Output an identity's secret key
  use         Set the default identity that will be used on all commands. This allows you to skip `--source-account` or setting a environment variable, while reusing this value in all commands that require it
  unset       Unset the default key identity defined previously with `keys use <identity>`

Options:
  -h, --help  Print help

Options (Global):
      --global                     ΓÜá∩╕Å Deprecated: global config is always on
      --config-dir <CONFIG_DIR>    Location of config directory. By default, it uses `$XDG_CONFIG_HOME/stellar` if set, falling back to `~/.config/stellar` otherwise. Contains configuration files, aliases, and other persistent settings
  -f, --filter-logs <FILTER_LOGS>  Filter logs output. To turn on `stellar_cli::log::footprint=debug` or off `=off`. Can also use env var `RUST_LOG`
  -q, --quiet                      Do not write logs to stderr including `INFO`
  -v, --verbose                    Log DEBUG events
      --very-verbose               Log DEBUG and TRACE events [aliases: --vv]
      --no-cache                   Do not cache your simulations and transactions [env: STELLAR_NO_CACHE=]
